你好  我叫钱德勒  刚搬到对面
Hi, my name's Chandler. l just moved in next door.
我想知道你是否有兴趣和我
And I was wondering if you would be interested
在末世后的世界里战斗
in battling me in a post-apocalyptic world
看谁能控制银河系剩余的能源
for control of the galaxy's last remaining energy source?
好啊  请进
Sure, neighbor! Come on in!
吉宁在吗
ls Janine around?
不在  她去上舞蹈课了
No, she's at dance class.
我可以看看她的房间吗
Can l check my room?
可以  但是别翻她的东西
Yeah, but, hey look, don't go through her stuff.
她会发飙的
She gets really mad.
天啊
Oh, my God!
一点男人住过的痕迹都没有
What is th...it's like a guy never lived in here.
小心  这个女性风格很危险
You gotta be careful. This girl thing is dangerous.
它已经扩散了
It's spreading already.
是吗
lt is?
这个粉红小抱枕是你的吗
ls this your pretty pink pillow on the couch?
不是
No.
那个什么都不能装的小盒子呢
ls that your tiny little box that's too small to put anything in?
-也不是  -不是
- No. - No!
情况很不妙  你是男人  好吗
Okay, this is not good. You are a guy, okay?
这是个"男人"的家
This is a "guy's" place.
如果你听之任之  你很快就会
If you let this go, you're going to be sitting around
开始做美甲了
with your fingers soaking in stuff.
你说得对  我会找她谈
All right, you're right. I'll talk to her.
找她谈  做个男子汉
Yes! Talk to her. Be a man!
-我是男子汉  -捍卫自己权益
- l'm a man. - Defend yourself!
钱德勒  快点  我们要缝防尘荷叶边
Chandler comes on. We have to hem the new dust ruffle.
我马上过去  亲爱的
Be right there, sweetums.
情况完全不同
Totally different situation.
你们好吗
Hey, guys.
跟希拉里吃饭吃得怎样
How was breakfast with Hillary?
还好  她还是有点沮丧
It was okay. She's still kind of depressed
她和他的男友刚分手了
because she broke up with her boyfriend.
-是你的辣妹助理主厨希拉里吗  -没错
- Well, is this Hillary your HOT assistant chef Hillary? - Yes.
我每次进去都盯着我的那个
The one that stares at me when l come in?
是你挡路而看过你一眼的那个
The one who looked at you once because you got in her way.
我还是看得出来  她对我有意思
Still, l could tell. She was into me.
你帮我们安排一下嘛
Why don't you set us up?
你要帮罗斯找对象吗
Are you setting Ross up with someone?
她有婚纱吗
Does she have a wedding dress?
瑞秋
Rachel?
我在为按摩店招揽新客做传单
Listen, I'm making up flyers to try to get new massage clients.
我可以去你布鲁明戴尔那里  用下复印机吗
So, can I come to Bloomingdale’s and use the copy machine?
可以  但他们会觉得奇怪
Sure, but they might think it's weird
因为我已经离职了
since l don't work there anymore.
天啊  怎么回事
Oh, my God! What happened?
我跳槽到拉夫·劳伦了
l got a job at Ralph Lauren.
太好了  恭喜你
Well, that's great! Congratulations!
都已经一年了
A year ago.
你都撑了一年  恭喜
You've lasted all year! Good for you.
菲比  你还是可以去我现在的公司复印
But, Pheebs, you can still use the copy machine where I actually work.
午休时间来  免得被我老板看到
But, just come by at lunch so my boss doesn't see you.
因为金会发飙  她本来就不太喜欢我
Cause Kim will just freak out. She already doesn't like me very much.
怪了  我的上司也不喜欢我
That's weird. I don't think my boss likes me either.
我的上司也不喜欢我
l don't think mine likes me either.
或许这是普遍现象
Maybe it's a universal thing.
或许因为现在是上班时间
Maybe because you're all hanging around here
你们却在这里谈天说笑
at 11 :30 on a Wednesday.
好吧  我们上班去了
Yeah, let's head off to work.
-谢谢  -不客气
- Thank you. - Sure.
说了你一定不信
Now you will not gonna believe this.
我在影印室影印时  拉夫·劳伦走了进来
But, I was in the copy room, making copies, and Ralph Lauren came in.
天啊  你有跟他说话吗
Oh, my God. Did you talk to him?
一点点  他人蛮好的
Yeah, a little. He seems really nice.
-吻功超棒  -什么
- Good kisser. - What?
什么
What?
-你亲了他  -没错
- You kissed him? - Totally.
-菲比  你说真的吗  -真的
Phoebe, are you serious? - Yes!
我刚进里面  他就进来自我介绍
Yeah. I was just in there. He came in and introduced himself
然后我们就亲热了
And the next thing I know, we're making out. You know.
菲比  你知道他已婚吧
Phoebe, you do know he's married?
不知道
No.
-菲比  -那我要怎么样嘛
- Phoebe. - What am I supposed to do?
难道每次跟男人亲热前  都要先问结婚没吗
Ask every guy l make out with if he's married?
对  我是该问
No. Yeah, l should.
乔伊
Hey, Joey.
可以跟你谈一下吗
Can l talk to you for a second?
照片里的这个小孩
There's a kid in this picture.
你认识他吗  他是你的亲戚还是什么吗
Do you know this kid? Is that like a relative or something?
不是  我只是觉得很可爱
No. l just thought it was cute.
我就怕这样  好
Yeah, that's what l was afraid of. Okay....
吉宁  我希望你住得愉快
Look, Janine, l really want you to feel at home here, but...
但你有些东西太女孩子气了
...some of this new stuff, it's too girlie.
比如什么
Like what?
比如这个  不认识的可爱宝宝的图片
Like this. Pictures of cute babies we don't know.
我们不能挂这种东西
We can't have that.
乔伊  那是安吉·帝斯  她是名艺术家
Joey, it's Anne Geddes. She's a famous artist.
我不认识这个宝宝
l don't know this baby.
我不知道她是不是名艺术家
l don't know if she's a famous artist or not.
我不想刁难你
l don't want to be a jerk,
-但你做的改变太多了  -对不起
- but you're changing too much around here. - l'm sorry.
我只是想让家里变漂亮点
I just thought I'd try to make the place a little nicer.
但是也太多了
But it's too much stuff.
你摆了蜡烛和这些绸绸缎缎的东西
You know, you got the candles and the "foofy schmoofer" thing here.
这里还有一幅浇花壶的画
Over here, you got a picture of a watering can.
我以为...
l just thought- -
我相信这个浇花壶一定很有名
l'm sure it's a famous watering can.
但是拜托啦
But come on.
浴室那个很烫的棒子是什么玩意
And what is with the really hot stick in the bathroom?
那是卷发器
lt's a curling iron.
那就没关系
Well, that's okay then.
还有我的浴巾  比如我走进浴室
Okay, my towels, for instance. l come into the bathroom...
我的浴巾却不在我常放的地板上
...and my towel is not on the floor, where l keep it.
而是挂在钩钩上
lt's up here on some hook.
而且味道都不一样了
And it smells different.
-它变干净了  -手感也不一样
- lt's clean. - lt feels different.
因为变干了
lt's dry.
好吧  我可以接受干净的浴巾
All right, l can make my peace with the clean, dry towels.
-还有这些小碎片是什么玩意  -不  不  不
- Okay, also what is with these chips you bought? - No, no, no
那是干燥花  是用来闻的
lt's potpourri. You're supposed to smell it.
好像碗里有个夏天
Well, that's like summer in a bowl.
金  你好
Kim, hi.
关于我交的那份行销报告
So you know, I...I handed in that marketing report
不知道你有何看法
and l never got to hear what you thought.
我没看
l didn't read it.
看来今年的春装一定很棒吧
So well, the spring line's really gonna be great this year, huh?
对
Yeah.
听说拉夫·劳伦在影印室  跟某人亲热
l hear Ralph Lauren fooled around with someone in the copy room.
从头说起
Tell me everything.
你们好
Hey, guys.
如何
What's up?
就是...
You know....
我的天
Oh, my God.
你的牙齿怎么了
What happened to your teeth?
我漂白了
l whitened them.
是吗
Really?
你们觉得呢
What do you think?
我觉得我不该直视它
l think l shouldn't look directly at them.
我是说真的
Come on, seriously.
也白得太夸张了吧
They're really, really, really white.
你以前的...
What was wrong with your old...
人类的牙齿不好吗
...human teeth?
我的确把漂白胶上得比较久
l did leave the gel on a little longer than it said to.
-多上了多久  -一天
- How much longer? - A day.
罗斯  你知道今晚要跟希拉里约会吧
Ross you know that tonight is your date with Hillary?
知道  所以我才漂白牙齿
l know. That's why l did it.
拜托  真的有那么糟吗
Come on. Are they really that bad?
不  完全不会
No, no no no.
放心好了  希拉里是瞎子吧
You'll be fine. Hillary's blind, right?
过了今晚就会被闪瞎了
She will be after tonight.
瑞秋  你有没有注意到...
Oh, hey, hey Rach, Do you notice anything- - ?
你的牙齿吗  我在外面就看到了
Your teeth? Yes, l saw them from outside.
说了你们绝对不信
You guys are never gonna believe this...
菲比跟拉夫·劳伦亲热了
...but Phoebe made out with Ralph Lauren.
-什么  -我的天
- What? - Oh, my God!
她在我的办公室偶遇他
She ran into him at my office,
然后他们就亲热了
and they just made out.
最扯的是
The craziest thing is,
我老板听我说完  就开始喜欢我
now my boss likes me because I told her about it
这是她今年听到最棒的八卦
and she said it was the best gossip she'd heard all year.
我今天真以我的朋友们为荣
l am proud of all my friends today.
天啊  菲比居然跟拉夫·劳伦亲热了
My God, Rachel, I can't believe Phoebe made out with Ralph Lauren.
真是忌妒死了
l'm so jealous!
你好  我是钱德勒  你同居男朋友
Hi, l'm Chandler, your live-in boyfriend.
钱德勒  拜托  别这样
Chandler, please. Come on.
你自己看
Look at him.
虽然我不是女人  不过他还真秀色可餐
Well, l am no woman, but that is one tasty dish.
拿去...
Here.
那个银发老帅哥是谁
Who's the silver fox?
那是你的亲热对象
That is your make-out buddy.
你不认得了吗
Don't you recognize him?
等等...
Oh, wait.
"菲比我爱你  吻我"
"Phoebe, l love you. Kiss me, please."
那才不是拉夫·劳伦
That's not Ralph Lauren.
不过声音像他
lt sounds like him, though.
-什么  -对啊  罗夫跟他一点也不像
- What? - Yeah, no, Ralph doesn't look anything like that guy.
他很年轻  长发落腮胡  背个大包包
He's young, and he's got long hair and a beard and a Hacky Sack- -
天啊  菲比  那不是拉夫·劳伦
Oh My God, Phoebe, that's not Ralph Lauren.
那是影印小弟肯尼
That's Kenny the copy guy!
什么
What?
完了  我还跟我老板说了这八卦
Oh Go... l told my boss that someone made out with Ralph Lauren.
要是她发现我骗她
lf she finds out that l lied to her,
一定会更讨厌我的  菲比
she'll hate me even more. Phoebe!
那个小弟为什么自称拉夫·劳伦啊
Why would the copy guy say he's Ralph Lauren?
好骗你跟他亲热啊
To get you to make out with him!
也许这件能压住你的白牙
Okay, maybe this will make them look less white.
不行
Nope.
好吧  没有用的颜色有
No. Okay, colors that don't work are...
蓝  黄  绿  红  黑  白  橘  紫
...blue, yellow, green, red, black, white, orange and purple.
我不知道该怎么办
What am I gonna do?
一小时后就要约会了
The date starts in like an hour.
罗斯  要是你的肤色白一点
Hey, maybe if your skin was lighter,
牙齿就不会那么显眼
your teeth wouldn't look so bright.
太好了  所以我去换肤就行了  谢谢你
Oh, great! So all l need to do is get some new skin. Thank you.
我是说你可以化一点妆
I say if we put just a little bit of makeup on you- -
我们已经不是十三岁了
We're not 13 anymore.
罗斯  只剩这个方法值得一试了
Ross, this is the only thing left that has a shot at working.
她不会发现我有化妆吗
Won't she notice l have makeup on?
拜托  半数的男人都有化妆
Please, half the guys out there have makeup on.
什么
What?
半数的人
Half the people.
我是说  你就试试看嘛
I mean- -  Just try it and see.
不要  我死也不化妆
No, I am not putting on makeup.
太好了  罗斯  帮我贴几张传单好吗
Hello? Ross, could you put up some of these flyers for me?
魔鬼  魔鬼
No! Demon! Demon!
这样抽屉就会香香的
Now our drawers will smell nice,
旧裤袜也没浪费
and we didn't waste these pantyhose
是啊  扔旧内衣会遭天打雷劈
Yes. God forbid we throw out old underwear.
我要去乔伊那边
You know what? l'm gonna go over to Joey's.
等等  我们还要整理装包装纸的抽屉呢
Wait, we're supposed to organize the wrapping paper drawer.
对  但我今天已经够女性化了
Yes, l've really gotten in touch with my feminine side enough today.
再缝一对香氛袋  我们就要变成女同志了
ln fact, we're two sachets away from becoming a lesbian couple.
今天的确很女孩子气
You know what? This has been kind of a girlie day.
-你说得对  抱歉  -不会啦
- You're right. l'm sorry. - Nah, Nah, it's okay.
不会  我只是想去男人的家
l just feel like l need to be in a "guy" place...
做男人做的事
...do kind of a "man" thing.
没错  去乔伊家吧
Yeah. Go over to Joey's.
去乔伊家喝啤酒捶墙壁吧
Go over to Joey's and drink some beer and hammer up some drywall.
男人聚在一起
You know when guys hang out
并非只会喝酒捶墙壁
they don't just drink beer and hammer up dry wall.
女生聚在一起  也不会穿内衣打枕头仗
When girls hang out, we don't have pillow fights in our underwear.
对不起  我们会  真的会
l'm sorry. We do.We do.
我不知道为什么说不会
l don't know why l said that.
钱德勒
Hey, Chandler.
进来  我们在织隔热手套呢
Come on in. We're knitting potholders.
不了  乔瑟芬
No, thanks, Josephine.
罗斯  我想说...
Ross, l was wondering if- -
天啊  男人都死哪去了
Oh, my God! Where are all the men?
-你好  金  -你好  瑞秋
- Hi, Kim. - Hi, Rachel.
记得我昨天说的事吗
Remember what happened yesterday?
其实根本没发生
Well, it didn't happen.
你没有取消台湾的布料订单吗
You didn't cancel the fabric order from Taiwan?
好  有两件事没发生
Okay, two things didn't happen.
我不是说有人在复印室跟拉夫·劳伦亲热吗
Remember I told you that someone made out with Ralph Lauren in the copy room?
事实证明是假的
Well, it turns out that's not true.
是假的呀  那就好玩了
lt's not true? That's interesting.
因为我去查过
Because l checked.
昨天午餐时间刷卡进影印室的
Only one keycard was used to access the copier yesterday during lunch,
只有你一个
and that keycard belonged to you, Rachel.
不  不  不是的  天啊
Oh no, no, no. Oh God,
你以为是我跟他亲热吗
You think l made out with him?
给我听着
Listen to me...
要是你以为跟拉夫上床  就能坐上我的位子
If you think sleeping with Ralph is going to get you my job.
你就错了
You are sadly mistaken.
我不想坐你的位子  真的
l don't want your job. l don't.
这真是天大的误会  我没跟他亲热
This is such a mistake. l didn't make out with him.
没人跟他亲热
Nobody made out with him.
我昨天没用我的卡
l didn't use my keycard yesterday.
我都不知道怎么用
l don't even know how to use my keycard.
-你好  罗夫  -你好  金
- Hi, Ralph. - Hi, Kim.
是啊  "什么都没发生"
Yeah. Nothing happened.
刚才的性张力都要一触即发了
You could cut the sexual tension in here with a knife.
之后我也只能去当厨师
And after that, what could l do except become a chef?
我希望将来能自己开家餐厅
And someday soon, I hope to open my own restaurant.
你很善于倾听
You know, you're a really great listener.
我交往过的男人多半讲个不停
Most guys l go out with, they talk and talk.
听到后来  真想叫他们闭嘴
After a while it's like, shut your mouth, you know?
我可能说太多了
I've probably been talking too much.
不如来聊下你吧
Why don't we talk about you a little bit?
说嘛  我想知道
Come on, l want to know.
好  我是长岛人
Okay. l'm from Long lsland.
来纽约念大学
l came to the city for college.
我有个五岁的儿子  平常闲暇时间
l have a 5-year-old son, and in my spare time...
喜欢看看谍报小说
...l like to read spy novels.
但我想多了解你
But let's talk more about you.
最棒的就是
So what's really neat?
如果先把花茎底部  在平底锅上烤一下
lf you sear the stems of the flowers first in a frying pan...
花就能开得更久
...your arrangement will look fresh much longer.
好棒的小秘诀
Joey, that is such a great tip!
莫妮卡  请你出去一下
Monica, could you excuse us for a second?
我有事找那位拿花的女士
l need to talk to the girl with the flowers.
乔伊  你待会过来
Okay. Oh but Joey, come over later
我要教你做喂鸟器
Because I'm going to teach you to make a bird feeder
只用松果和花生酱就行哦
out of just a pine cone and some peanut butter.
我最喜欢鸟了
l love birds.
你在搞什么啊
What is the matter with you?
-什么  -你在插花
- What? - You're arranging flowers!
你这里有干花
You got dead flowers!
你还挂穿得一朵花的宝宝照片
You've got a picture of a baby dressed like flowers!
这不是乔伊
This is not Joey!
我还是乔伊  好吗
Hey, hey look, l am still Joey, okay?
花只不过是很好看嘛
Flowers, they're just nice to look at.
那是一个名摄影师画的
And that happens to be a picture by a famous artist
宝宝也很有名
of a famous baby.
你正在变成女人
You're turning into a woman.
我没有
No, l'm not.
你怎么这么说  好过分哦
Why would you say that? That's just mean.
我惹你生气了  我说了什么
Now l've upset you? What did l say?
不是你说了什么  而是你的口气
lt's not what you said. lt's the way you said it.
我的天
Oh, my God!
我是女人
l'm a woman!
现在她觉得是我跟他亲热
So now, she thinks that I made out with him
是为了夺她的位
and I did it to get her job.
-你怎么不跟她说实话  -我说了
- Why didn't you just tell the truth? - l did.
但是她觉得不会有人蠢到
But she doesn't think anyone would be stupid enough
把影印小弟当成拉夫·劳伦
to confuse Kenny the copy guy with Ralph Lauren.
如果肯尼才是公司的幕后老板呢
What if Kenny were the real brains behind the whole company?
搞不好拉夫·劳伦
You know? What if Kenny hired that Ralph guy
只是肯尼请来当幕前的人
to be the pretty front man, huh?
她想过这个问题吗
Did she ever think of that?
你今天跟肯尼约会了吧
You were with Kenny today, weren't you?
只有一下下而已
Just for a second.
菲比  我该怎么办
Phoebe, what am l gonna do?
你只好跟拉夫·劳伦上床了
The only thing you can do. Sleep with Ralph Lauren.
我才不跟拉夫·劳伦上床
l'm not gonna sleep with Ralph Lauren.
我可以  但是我不会
l mean, l could, but l wouldn't.
那跟肯尼上床吧
Sleep with Kenny.
-那样对我也没好处  -好处可大了
- That wouldn't help me. - Oh, yes, it would.
今晚我真的很开心
l've had a really good time tonight.
我很少第一次约会  就感到如此心有灵犀
You know, l rarely connect with someone this much on the first date.
我也是
Me neither.
我今晚也过得很开心
l've had a really good time too, you know.
你要吃那块面包吗
Are you gonna eat that bread?
我只是喜欢闻那味道
l just like the smell.
你好好笑
You make me laugh.
要不要去沙发上坐一下
Would you like to move to the couch?
或许我该把灯光调暗一点
Maybe l'll just turn down the lights a little?
干脆关灯如何
How about all the way?
好
Okay.
好酷的海报
Wow, cool poster.
还是要说"好亮眼的海报"
Or should l say, "groovy poster"?
这样啊
So...
刚才聊到哪了
...where were we?
那是你的牙齿吗
Are those your teeth?
你看得见是吧
You can see them, huh?
对  白得很吓人
Yes. They're insanely white.
我特地为你漂白的
l did that for you.
你有毛病吗
What's the matter with you?
你居然说我有毛病
What's the matter with me?
你还装黑光灯呢  都1999年了
You've got a black light. lt's 1999!
太好了  金
Oh, good. Kim, hi.
瑞秋  我一直想问你
Hi, Rachel.  I've been meaning to ask you.
你看过拉夫·劳伦的新床单了吗
have you seen the new Ralph Lauren sheets?
我在想什么  你当然看过
What am l thinking? Of course you have.
好
Okay, look.
很抱歉之前对你说谎
l'm sorry that l lied to you before.
你猜得没错
You were right.
拉夫和我交往过  但已经结束了
Ralph and l were an item, but we're not anymore.
是吗
Oh, really?
对  他甩了我
Yeah, he dumped me.
他说"瑞秋  我不能这样"
He said, "Rachel, l can't do this.
"虽然你是个很美
Even though you're a very, very...
很美的女人"
...very beautiful woman...
"我不能这样  我有家室  对不起"
...l can't do this. l'm married and l'm sorry."
不知为何他还说  "你永远也不会升职"
But he said, "And you will never get promoted...
尤其不可能高于金  她是拉夫·劳伦体系
...especially not above Kim, who is an integral cog...
最不可或缺的重要人物"
...in the Ralph Lauren machine."
你以为我会相信...
You expect me to believe- -
-你好  拉夫  -你好  金
- Hi, Ralph. - Hi, Kim.
天啊
Oh, my God.
他看你的眼神好冷酷
He gave you the coldest look l've ever seen.
仿佛对你恨之入骨
lt's like he hates you!
所以是真的咯
Then it is true!
当然是真的  我好难过哦
Of course it's true. And it hurts so bad.
小可怜  过来
Oh, honey, come here.
你会没事的
Oh, it'll be okay.
你的心情我懂
We've all been there.
你和拉夫有过一段吗
You and Ralph?
影印小弟肯尼
Kenny the copy boy.
我有事要说
I need to talk to you.
怎么了  你心情不好吗
What's the matter? You upset?
我们得把这些女生的东西扔掉
I'm sorry, but we gotta get rid of all this girlie stuff in here.
我得当个男人
l gotta be a man!
客厅必须维持男人的风格  懂吗
Okay? The living room has to remain a guy place, okay?
必须得这样
That's the way it has to be.
如果你非要这样  我就拿回我房里
Well, if that's what you want. l'll just put it all in my room.
好  很好
Good. Great.
谢谢你的谅解
And thanks for being so understanding.
我不想把场面搞得很难看
l didn't want to make a big deal out of this.
宝宝的照片可以挂到我房里
But you could put the picture of the famous baby in my room.
如果你想的话
l mean, if you want to.
好
Okay.
浇花壶的画也可以
And maybe the watering can there.
好
Sure.
还有一两个小盒子
And a couple of these little tiny boxes.
乔伊  要不要都放到你房里啊
Joey, do you want me to put it all in your room?
好吧
Okay.